

EBY CHACKO

Full Stack developer

+353 89 233 6291

cybe1990@gmail.com

Pallinasloe, Co Galway, IE

linkedin.com/in/eby-chacko-85695b245

EDUCATION

Deploma In Full Stack development Code Institute

2023 - 2024

BCA(Computer Application) Ilahia College Of Arts & Science 2012 - 2015 Grade: B

Master Diploma In Animation Cochin Cadd Center

2007 - 2009 Grade: A

Higher Secondary (Biology/Maths) St. Stephens's HSS

2007 - 2009 Grade: A

SSLC MDH School 2005 Grade: A

Summary

I am a Full stack developer with Almost 7 years of experience in graphic design. I have a passion for creating innovative solutions that meet the needs of clients. With 7 years of experience in graphic design and sales, I have developed strong communication skills that allow me to work effectively with clients and team members. My technical skills include proficiency in Python, JavaScript, HTML/CSS, and SQL.

I am seeking a position at any IT section where I can continue to develop my skills and contribute to the success of the team.

Experience

• Aug 2022 - Present (1 year 3 months) Shearwater Hotel &Spa

Night Porter

The job responsibilities of a Night Porter include guest care, reception duties, phone answering, dealing with guest queries, and general cleaning. Working as a Night Porter would provide an opportunity to gain work experience in the hospitality industry. I am doing this job as part-time, because I am student of full stack development course in Code Institute.

Jan 2021 - Feb 2022 (1 year 2 months)
Color dots flex and vinyl printing

Graphic Designer

The job responsibility was to create a design based on the customer requirements using design software photoshop.

Jun 2016 - Jun 2020 (4 years 1 month)
Landmark International Auto Spare Parts Trading LLC

Sales Executive

Started working as a store keeper. Because of my computer skill, the GM promoted me as sales executive.

Responsibilities

- 1. Inspecting, labelling, and placing products on shelves
- 2. Supervising staff and keeping records of sales
- 3. Managing the Tills and Account.
- May 2015 May 2016 (1 year 1 month)
 Color dots flex and vinyl printing

Graphic Designer

The job responsibility was to create a design based on the customer requirements using design software photoshop.

EXPERTISE

SQL / NoSQL

django / Python

JavaScript / jQuery

HTML/HTML5

CSS

Adobe Photoshop

Adobe Premier pro

CorelDRAW

3Ds Max

LANGUAGES

Malayalam

English

Hindi

Urdu

Mar 2011 - Mar 2012 (1 year 1 month)

Page3 Digital media

Graphic Designer / Video Editor

Page 3 Digital media is a digital firm that have a modelling photo studio and have a lot of wedding video and photo works. I worked as the manager, as well as the graphic designer and video editor.

Oct 2010 - Mar 2011 (6 months)
Guinnes digital communications

Graphic Designer

Job responsibility was Colour coding the Photos taken in the studio using deferent colour correcting softwares like photoshop, Lightroom etc.

Jul 2009 - Sep 2010 (1 year 3 months)
Excel laser colorlab and studio

Graphic Designer

Old Photo Restoration, Creative designs, Album Design, Flyer design etc.

Jun 2008 - Jun 2009 (1 year 1 month)
Vithayathil digital color lab

Graphic Designer

Album Designing, Flyer Designs, Visiting Card Designs

Declaration

I Eby Chacko, declare that the information provided in this document is true to the best of my knowledge and belief. I have carefully documented my educational qualifications, work experience, and skills.

Date	:	Eby Chack
Place	· t	EDY CHUCK